MATTHEW FASANO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Phone: 203-260-3873 E-mail: matt.fasano88@gmail.com Website: chakafasano88.github.io/portfolio

SUMMARY

Software Developer with 2 years experience building full-stack applications for web, mobile, and SaaS environments in collaboration with seasoned designers, backend engineers, and mobile developers. Skilled in replicating UI/UX wireframes, creating REST API requests, and has a passion for learning new frameworks that drive innovation possibilities in the tech community.

SKILLS

- HTML

- Javascript
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- React
- Nexis
- PHP

- CSS
- Git
- React/Native AngularJS
- Apollo Redux
- GraphQL MySQL

EXPERIENCE

VENTURETEC - STAMFORD, CT

December 2017 to Present

Fullstack Developer with a focus on frontend developement.

MOBILE DEVELOPER Agrellus - A market place for farmers - March 2018 - July 2018

- Implemented software design wire-frames.
- Connected with client made API using React Native & Redux to manipulate data.
- Setup credit card and bank account payments using Stripejs.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER Leasenet - Property management software - March 2018 - July 2018

- Constructed the complete frontend Admin portal with AngularJS, HTML, CSS.
- .Assisted in creating backend data structures and database creation.
- Implemented software design wireframes
- Assistied in database creation and optimization

PROJECTS

LEAD DEVELOPER FocusLoop - Financial Blog - May 2019 - Present

- Collaborating with visionary on application goals, target users, UI/UX.
- Developed with React, Apollo, GraphQL, Yoga, and Prisma.
- User Authtentication, email updates, user permissions, rich text editor, liking and commenting articles.

EDUCATION

New York Code & Design Academy

March 2017 - June 2017

St. Michael's College Colchester, VT Bachelors in English Literature and Music

September 2007 - June 2011